# **DIMAS PERCEKA**

# GIS | REMOTE SENSING

Teras Country, J.11 Tonjong (+62)85236257722 ugadimas@gmail.com

## PROFILE SUMMARY

I have 5 years experience in GIS and Remote Sensing. In my last project, I manage development and implementation of software to facilitate the control and collecting of data mapping, inspection, quantity performance, schedule performance, support the design and development of GIS component, dataservice, and support capacity planning to accommodate new/emerging GIS technologies to meet Customer need.

## REFFERENCE

Wikha Jily Fary [GIS Developer Lead at Koltiva]

Email: wikha.jily@koltiva.com

Benita Nathania [Senior Researcher Lead at WRI]

Email: benita.nathania@wri.org

#### EDUCATION

# Geomatics Engineering [Master of Engineering]

2018 - 2021

Universitas Gadjah Mada, Yogyakarta Indonesia

Master Thesis Title: Development of Spatial Web Based

Agricultural Irrigation Management Information System

## Soil Science [Bachelor Degree]

2012 - 2012

Universitas Gadjah Mada, Yogyakarta Indonesia

Lorem Bachelor Thesis: Labile and Stable Fraction of Carbon in

Different Landuse

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Remote Sensing and Climate Lead**

January, 2022 - Now

## Koltiva AG, Jakarta Indonesia

- Develop and manage remote sensing projects that contribute to climate change analysis and environmental monitoring.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams including data scientists, GIS specialists, and environmental experts to design and implement innovative climate solutions.
- Provide expert analysis on remote sensing data to inform policy making and strategic environmental planning.
- Lead the integration of remote sensing data with climate models to predict and assess environmental changes and impacts.
- Ensure compliance with all relevant environmental regulations and standards

#### **GIS Developer**

March, 2019 - January, 2021

## World Resources Institute, Jakarta Indonesia

- Work directly with Product Owners to translate business needs to technical requirements and specifications
- Work closely with stakeholders and provide the deliverables with high quality of standards
- · Develop, test, and deploy automated prioritization script
- Participates in the design, development and implementation of complex applications
- As needed, coordinated with existing team of sustainable commodities researchers

#### **GIS Developer**

March, 2017 - January, 2019

## Center of Agroecology and Land Resources, Yogyakarta

- Project for Connectivity of Protected Areas and Peat Ecosystem Cultivation in Central Kalimantan
- Perform data capture and analysis for GIS product
- Support in designing and creating the geospatial database
- Perform data capture and analysis for GIS product
- Project for Inventarisation of Peat Ecosystem Cultivation in Lamandau, Central Kalimantan
- Participates in the design, development and implementation of complex applications
- As needed, coordinated with existing team of sustainable commodities researchers

# **GIS Specialist [By Project]**

July, 2016 - February, 2017

## Waindo Specterra

- Survey of chemical, biological and physical characteristics of soil for Land System in East and South Kalimantan
- Perform data capture and analysis for GIS product
- Support in designing and creating the geospatial database

## **GIS Specialist [By Project]**

January, 2016 - July, 2016

## Agricola Nusantara Baramineral

- Project for Technical Feasibility Study on Industrial Scale Vaname Shrimp Farming in Lingga Islands, Riau
- Manage geospatial database and develop maps and aerial photogrammetry
- Perform data capture and analysis for GIS product
- Support in designing and creating the geospatial database
- Oversee data flow, management, and distribution activities to support GIS

## CERTIFICATE

• sUAS Remote Pilot March, 2020 – June, 2020

Direktorat Kelaikudaraan dan Pengoperasian Pesawat Udara

National UAV Photogrammetry of 3D Model Reconstruction
 Geomatics Engineering, National Cheng Kung University, Taiwan

• Interactivity with Javascript and Python

Michigan University, United States

January, 2020

## TECHNICAL SKILL

## • GIS Software

ArcGIS Pro | ArcGIS City Engine | Quantum GIS

# • Remote Sensing Software

ENVI | ENVI LiDAR | IDRISI | ERDAS | SAGA GIS | Global Mapper

## • Cloud Processing

Google Earth Engine | Kaggle | Google Colab

## CAD Software

Autocad | Autocad Map | Autodesk Revit

## • 3D Modelling Software

Agisoft Metashape

# • Programming Language

Python | Javascript | HTML | CSS | PHP

# • Database Management System

PostgreSQL | MySQL | MongoDB